http://www.tesia.com/privacy-policy

Tesia Privacy Policy
Last Updated Date: 7/14/20We have updated our Privacy Policy. By continuing to use the site, you agree to our new terms.
This privacy policy describes the information Tesia Clearinghouse, LLC collects about you and how it is used or shared, what rights and choices you have over your personal information, and measures we take to protect your information. This privacy policy applies to personal information collected by or on behalf of Tesia Clearinghouse, LLC (“Tesia,” “we” or “us”) through our website https://tesia.com website and mobile versions of our website (collectively, the “Site”), by phone or other offline contacts and anywhere else we display this privacy policy. By using the Site, you accept the terms of this privacy policy in effect at the time of your visit.
Personal Information We Collect from the Site
Personal information is information directly or indirectly identifies you or can be used to identify you as an individual. The following are the categories of information we collect through the Site and how we collect it:
• Information you provide. You may provide personal information to us when you use the Site. For example, you may provide your contact information such as your name, e-mail address, or telephone number when you contact us through the Site. You can choose not to give us your personal information but in some cases, we will not be able to respond to your request or answer your questions without certain contact information.
• Information collected automatically. We may automatically collect certain information about you or your device when you visit or interact with the Site using tools such as pixels, log files or “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on your browser when you visit the Site that collect information about your use of the Site to help us improve your access to the Site and the services we provide. This information typically remains in aggregate form and does not identify individual users. If a combination of information we collect does identify you as individual, we will treat the combined information as personal information. The information we collect using pixels, log files and cookies may include information such as IP address, device ID, browser type and other information associated with your device or the pages you interact with on the Site. We use this information in aggregate form to enhance the experience and operation of the Site, analyze trends such as Site usage, to administer and secure the Site, and to evaluate the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns on other platforms. You can adjust your browser settings to accept or reject cookies; however, if you disable all cookies, you may not be able to access all features of the Site. We do not permit third parties to track your online activities over time and across other websites based on your use of the Site.
The Site also uses analytics tools such as Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. that uses cookies to help the Site analyze how users navigate the Site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Site (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google in aggregate form. Google uses this aggregated information on our behalf in order to evaluate use of the Site, compile reports on Site activity and other services relating to Site usage. You can learn more about Google Analytics and how to opt out here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
How We Use Your Information
We use your personal information to accomplish our business and commercial purposes, including to:
• Respond to your questions or requests, to send you information about our products or services we think may be of interest to you, or to otherwise communicate with you. You can opt out of email marketing communications from us at any time by using the unsubscribe link in our emails or you can email us at info@tesia.com.
• Provide and improve our products, services and the Site.
• Protect the security of the Site.
• Comply with our legal obligations or to respond to law enforcement or legal or regulatory inquires or requests or legal proceedings.
• Protect our legal rights, your health and safety or the health and safety of our employees or others.
When We Share Your Information
Except as described in this privacy policy, we do not sell, share or rent your personal information without your consent. We may share your personal information with the following categories of recipients:
• Service providers that help us provide the Site, our products and services or help us operate our business. Service providers are contractually required to secure your information and prohibited from using the information for their own purposes.
• We reserve the right to disclose your information to a successor entity in the event of a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate changes to Tesia.
• Other third parties as necessary to protect your safety or the safety of others, to protect our legal interests or to comply with applicable laws and regulations or our legal requirements.
How We Protect Your Information
We maintain commercially reasonable safeguards to help protect personal information from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, information transmitted over the Internet cannot be 100% secured and we do not guarantee your information will be secure from theft, loss or unauthorized access or use.
Third-party Links
We may provide links on the Site to third-party websites we think may be of interest to you, including links to social media sites. These websites are independent from Tesia and the Site and have their own separate privacy policies and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such third-party websites.
Do-Not-Track Signals
Some browsers have “do-not-track” features that allow you to tell a website not to track you. These features are not all uniform. The Site does not currently respond to browser-based “do-not-track” signals.
Your Rights and Choices
• Communication Preferences. You may opt out of receiving communications from us at any time by contacting us using the methods listed in the Contact Us section at the bottom of this privacy policy or by using the unsubscribe links included in communications from us. Please note that even if you unsubscribe from our marketing communications, you may still receive emails, mailings or other communications related to your transactions with us.
• Correction and Amendment. You may update or amend your information by contacting us via the email address or phone number included in the Contact Us section at the bottom of this privacy policy.
Children’s Privacy
The Site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone we know to be under the age of 13 through the Site. If we become aware that a child under age 13 has provided personal information through the Site, we will delete such information from our files.
International Users
Tesia and its affiliated companies are based in the United States. Our services and the Site are not targeted at individuals outside the United States. If you are visiting the Site from outside the United States and provide us with personal information, please note that your information may be accessed or transferred, stored and processed by Tesia or its affiliated companies or service providers in the United States. The data protection or privacy laws in the United States may be different than those in your country. By doing business with or interacting with Tesia or our Site, you acknowledge and agree to the transfer of your personal information to facilities located in the United States and understand that such information will be stored and processed in accordance with this privacy policy and the laws of the United States.
Notice to Residents of California
The information in this section applies to residents of California with regard to personal information subject to this privacy policy. If you have any questions about this privacy policy or would like to receive a printed copy, please contact us at privacy@vynecorp.com.
• How We Collect and Use Personal Information. In accordance with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”), this section describes the personal information we collected about California residents in the last 12 months, the sources of that information, our business or commercial purposes for collecting the information, and the third parties with whom we shared that information. Please refer to the corresponding sections of this policy above for details on the following:
- Personal Information We Collect from the Site: This section describes the categories of personal information we collected and the categories of sources from which the information was collected. Please see the “Personal Information We Collect from the Site” section above for more information.
- How We Use Your Information: This section describes the business or commercial purposes for which we collected the information. Please see the “How We Use Your Information” section above for more information.
- When We Share Your Information: This section lists the categories of third parties with whom we shared personal information. Please see the “When We Share Your Information” section above for more information.
• Your Rights and How to Exercise Them. Under the CCPA, California residents have certain rights with regard to their personal information. Those rights may only apply in certain circumstances and may be subject to limitations or exceptions. A summary of those rights is provided below as well as information on how to exercise your rights. Please note that we will require certain identifying information about you as necessary for us to verify your request in accordance with applicable law.
- Right to Know: You have the right to ask us to tell you the categories of personal information we collected, the purposes for which we collected, sold or disclosed that information, and the categories of third parties to whom we disclosed the information in the last 12 months. To exercise this right, please call us toll-free at (877) 323-0312 or email your request to privacy@vynecorp.com and include “Disclosure Request” in the subject line of your message.
- Right to Access: You have the right to access the personal information specific to you individually, that we collected, used, disclosed and/or sold about you in the last 12 months. To exercise this right, please call us toll-free at (877) 323-0312 or email your request to privacy@vynecorp.com and include “Access Request” in the subject line of your message.
- Right to Delete: You have the right to request us to delete the personal information we have collected or maintain about you. Please note that certain exceptions may apply to your right to delete information, such as when we must retain personal information as required or permitted by law and we will also maintain a record of your deletion request. We will notify you if any such exceptions apply to your request. To exercise this right, please call us toll-free at (877) 323-0312 or email your request to privacy@vynecorp.com and include “Deletion Request” in the subject line of your message.
We do not discriminate against you for requesting any of the rights noted above. However, we may offer certain financial incentives, charge reasonable fees related to your requests, or deny your right to know, right to access or right to deletion in accordance with applicable law.
You can exercise these rights yourself or you can designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. If you would like an authorized agent to submit a request on your behalf, please send us an email at privacy@vynecorp.com for instructions and details on proof and information required for use of an authorized agent.
• How We Disclose Information. We disclosed personal information to third parties for business purposes during the last 12 months. For more information on the categories of information we disclosed and to whom it was disclosed, see the “When We Share Your Information” section above. We do not sell your personal information or the personal information of minors under age 16.
• Third-Party Marketing Disclosure. Under California Civil Code § 1798.83, California residents with whom we have a business relationship can request information about the types of personal information, if any, we shared with third parties for the direct marketing purposes of the third parties and the identities of the third parties with whom we shared such information in the last 12 months. We do not share your personal information with third parties in this manner and have not done so in the last 12 months. You may request more information by contacting us using the contact information at the bottom of this privacy policy.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time and may apply changes to previously collected information, as permitted by applicable law. Any updates to this privacy policy will be posted on the Site and we will indicate the last updated date of the changes. Your continued use of the Site means you accept those changes as of the posted updated date.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us via toll-free telephone at (877) 323-0312, by email to privacy@vynecorp.com or by mail at:
Attention: Privacy
100 Ashford Center North, Suite 300
Dunwoody, GA 30338
